Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1948-2015; 1990-2015; Accession 2017-A-031
  - 2008 Commencement Binder contents (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Commencement 2008 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 2007 Commencement Binder (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 2007 Commencement (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 2006 Commencement Binder (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Commencement 2006 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 2005 Commencement Binder (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 2005 Commencement--May 23 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Commencement 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commencement 2004--Helene Gayle (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2003 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Commencement 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2003 Commencement Speakers: Jeffrey Koplan (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2002 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Commencement 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2001 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2001 Commencement (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2000 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2000 Commencement (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Geeta Rao Gupta: commencement speaker, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1999 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Commencement 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1998 Commencement Binder (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Commencement 1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Commencement May 26, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Commencement 1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Guests at EPH 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Dean correspondence 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NIH Visit Dec. 5-6, 1995: Ellen Stover/Leonard Mitnick (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - C. Everett Koop, M.D., SC.D. October 29-30, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - C. Everett Koop/M. Merson: Breakfast: Quinnipiac Club 7:30 AM Wed., Oct. 30, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - C. Everett Koop, MD: Time Life Initiative, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - December 9, 1996: Allan Rosefield, Dean, Columbia University (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Karolinska Institutet: June 17, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - January 23, 1997: Dr. Cuadrado (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - February 1998: Thai Princess to Visit Yale (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - April 14, 1999: Richard Blumenthal (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Feb 24, 1999: Frank Ruddle, M.D. Public Health Grand Rounds (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Jan. 27, 1999: Barry Levy, M.D. Public Health Grand Rounds (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - December 1, 1999 Joxel Garcia (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - October 20, 1999: 9:00 AM: James Comer, M.D. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - October 4, 1999 Lawrence Wallack (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - February 23, 2000: Cathy Cohen (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Grand Rounds Working File, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - February 15, 2000 Dr. David Brandling-Bennett (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - February 2, 2000 Ruth Katz (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - April 6, 2001 Fernando Zacarias (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - April 10, 2001 Gilbert Omenn (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Disparities Symposium 2001 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Connecticut Hospice Keynote Address: June 2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Doctors Without Borders 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Hollywood and Big Tobacco, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Lecture: Edward Kaplan, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Communications: Rita Sands, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Senator Lieberman 9/1/04, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Galvin Visit 3/31/05, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Lecture: James Repace: April 19, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dean's Lecture: Ron Kessler: 11/13/06, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Lecture: Howard Koh: 3/8/07, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Lecture: Eric Whitaker: 11/09, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sir Michael Marmot, Dean's Lecture 3/25/10, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Barbara Wolfe, Dean's Lecture: 4/21/10, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dean's Lecture: Jewel Mullen April 4, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Lecture: Tom Scully: Spring 2011 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Lecture: Peter Hotez: 9/30/11, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Adrian Ostfeld Memorial Lecture with Program on Aging--12/7/11, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Breast Cancer Screening Panel 4/12/12, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Lecture: Vincent Mor: 10/3/12, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Lecture: Donnelly: 10/18/12, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dean's Lecture: Beyrer: 11/29/12, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Lecture: Unni Karunakara: April 24, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Lecture/Aging Seminar: Judith Kasper: October 2, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Dean's Lecture: Barry Bloom: 4/17/2014 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Lecture: October 1, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 2000 Distinguished Alumni Award: Debra Haffner (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - November 10, 2000: Bill Kissick (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - January 14, 1999: EPH Alumni/Annual Fund Plan (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - November 30, 1998: Denmark Health Officials (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - AYAPH EMAC: Faculty Recruitment Proposal, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - AYAPH Winter Board Meeting: 12:30: 2/4/05, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Meetings, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Day 2002: 6/7/02 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - June 2, 2000: Alumni Reunion (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - June 5-6, 1998: Alumni Weekend (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - EPH Alumni Reunion: 1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - EPH 50th Alumni Anniversary: June 6, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Yale School of Public Health Nancy G. Hildreth Chronic Disease Epidemiology Library Fund, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - EPH Alumni Fund, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 2005 State of the School Letters (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 2004 State of the School Letter (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - State of the School: 2003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - State of School: 2002 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - State of the School letter: 2001 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - State of the School Letter: 2000 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - '99 State of the School letter, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Alumni Letter 1998 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dean's Letter: October 1997, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dean's Letter: Sept., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - September 1995: Alumni letter "master copy" (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Alumni Letter: May (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal Letter, Fall 2009 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal Letter, Fall 2010 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal Letter, Fall 2011 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal Letters, Fall 2012 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal Letters, Fall 2013 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Alumni Fund Appeal, Fall 2014 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Honor Roll of Donors Alumni 2009 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Honor Roll of Donors Alumni 2010 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Honor Roll of Donors Alumni 2011 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Honor Roll of Donors Alumni 2012 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Alumni Communications (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - 2015 Annual Letter (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Biostatistics-faculty salaries, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - EPH Annual Reports and Data
    - 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 13-15)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - 2004 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
    - Faculty Annual Reports by Division
      - 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
      - 2007 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health faculty publications, 1984-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health faculty research and publications, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Global Health Faculty Salaries, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Personal Commentary: Michael Merson, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee: Agendas, meeting minutes and correspondence
    - 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 2003 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 2006 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Appointments and Promotions Committee: Agendas, meeting minutes and correspondence
    - 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 2000 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
    - 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
    - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5-8)
    - 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
    - 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
  - Committee of Permanent Officers: faculty meetings, minutes, agendas and correspondence
    - 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee: agendas, meeting minutes, and correspondence
    - 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
    - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
    - 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
    - 2000 (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
    - 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
    - 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - 2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 2006 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Turner Committee report: June 30 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Yale Public Health Newsletters (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - George Silver memorial materials (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Five-year plan: Division of Health Policy and Resources, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - EPH Strategic Planning Committee, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Schweiker Report to Congress: Hospital Prospective Payment for Medicare: 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mission of the Dept. of Epidemiology and Public Health: Current Activities: 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Department reports and objectives, 1980-1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum Guidelines, Departmental Descriptions (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Photos, 1999-2008 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Curriculum Guidelines, Departmental Descriptions, 1971-1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Wienerman Committee meetings
    - 1996 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 1997 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - 1998 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Weinderman Memorial Reading Room: Dedication Ceremony guest book, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Weinerman Fellowship
    - 2001 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - 2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 2003 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 2006 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 2007 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Yale Project for Health Action-research and correspondence, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hartford Foundation Proposal and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Medicine/Public Health Initiative: Correspondence and Summary, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Merson meeting with NH Chief of Police Pastore, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Yale BIC meeting, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Meeting and Correspondence regarding Yale/Union School of Public Health Collaboration, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Baranovsky, Procter Gamble Yale visit, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Some Aspects of Regional Hospital Affiliations Some Aspects of Regional Hospital Affiliations, 1985-1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Kent Buse Kent Buse meeting correspondence; draft of report on HIV prevalence patterns in urban India, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - China Correspondence and documents regarding Union School of Public Health in Beijing, China collaboration, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alumni and development: notes, research, and correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - EPH events: correspondence and ephemera, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - CDC training program at Yale: proposal, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Brandon Brei coverage, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - John D. Thompson: correspondence and administrative records, 1948-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Faculty voting
    - 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - First cancer control research unit for Connecticut at Yale grant, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Second cancer control research unit for Connecticut at Yale grant, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Third Cancer control research unit for Connecticut at Yale grant, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Cancer trends and cancer prevention research in Connecticut: statistical and epidemiological report, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - EPH proposals and reports, 1989-2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - YSPH Winslow Medal Posters, 2010-2015 (Box 18)
  - Winslow Medal (DVD-Video), 2004; 2017-A-0031-0002; 1 (Box 20)
- Alumni Affairs Office records, 1975-2016; Accession 2017-A-073
  Restricted until January 1, 2052
  - Association of Schools Public Health Reports
    - 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - EPH Today newsletter
    - 1996 Fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1998 Fall (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1999 Spring (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 2000 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 2001 Spring (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 2002 Spring (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 2002 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 2003 Fall (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 2003 Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 2004 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 2004 Spring (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 2005 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 2005 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 2006 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 2006 Spring (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 2007 Spring (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 2008 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Magazine Spring 2009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - @YSPH Summer 2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - @YSPH Fall 2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - @YSPH Winter 2013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Health Careers Opportunities Program (HCOP): Pathways, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - HCOP Site Visit, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - HCOP Application & Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - HCOP Grant Copy, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - HCOP Grant Copy: Year 1, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - HCOP Grant Copy: Year 2, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - HCOP Grant Copy: Year 3, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - HCOP First Renewal Attempt, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Final Progress Report HCOP, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - HCOP Pathways Study Q2 Y3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - HCOP Update, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1997 Library Grant (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - GAP Analysis, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Study of Training Needs in the CT Dept. of Public Health, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 96 Urban Health Program, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract (HRSA), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration Contract, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - HRSA #5--Final, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - HCOP Proposals and Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Traineeships, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Traineeships, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Traineeships, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Traineeships, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Traineeships, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Traineeships, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract: 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract: 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract: 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - UI-Chicago PHP Grant Minority Evaluation: 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract: 1995: extension (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Department of Public Health and Addiction Services/Epidemiology Public Health Survey 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Public Health Practice Leadership Survey, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Department of Public Health and Addiction Services/Epidemiology Public Health Agreement, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract: 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - UI-Chicago Public Health Practice contract 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 10-10A)
  - ASPH/HRSA Cooperative Agreement Subaward Project, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Coop Grant: 1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Coop Grant: 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chiropractic Grant: 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chiropractic Grant: Six-Month Extension Request, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Urban Health Program Grant, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Day
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 2005 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 2006 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 2008 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 2009 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 2010 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 2011 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 2012 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 2013 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 2014 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 2015 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 2016 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - CT Healthy Family Proposal: 2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Report on Continuing Education and Distance Learning Faculty Survey: University of Connecticut, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Connecticut Statewide Partnership for Public Health Workforce Development, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Community Projects (CP)
    - Descriptions, 1986-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Creed Steele Scholarships, 2000-2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lowell Levin Award, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Scott Award, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Board Scholarship, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Yale University School of Public Health Self-Study, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - YSPH Appendices to Self-Study, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1980 CEPH Accreditation (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Reaccreditation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1980 CEPH Accreditation 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 1975 Original CEPH Accreditation (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1985 CEPH Reaccreditation, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Computer files
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - Computer files [born digital] (Box 5)
      - Emergency Preparedness 101, 2017-A-0073-0001; 1 (Box 5)
      - Managing Emergencies and Disasters Using the Incident Command System, 2017-A-0073-0002; 1 (Box 5)
      - Emergency Preparedness 201, 2017-A-0073-0003; 1 (Box 5)
      - Applied Epidemiology for Public Health Nurses, 2017-A-0073-0004; 1 (Box 5)
      - Emergency Preparedness for PH Nurses, 2017-A-0073-0005; 1 (Box 5)
      - Syndromic Surveillance Methods and Applications, 2017-A-0073-0006; 1 (Box 5)
      - Emergency Preparedness for Nursing Educators, 2017-A-0073-0007; 1 (Box 5)
      - Disaster Preparedenss for School Nurses (Master), 2017-A-0073-0008; 1 (Box 5)
      - Disaster Preparedenss for School Nurses (Updated Master), 2017-A-0073-0009; 1 (Box 5)
      - Emergency and Crisis Risk Communication, 2017-A-0073-0010; 1 (Box 5)